W. Dean Edwards collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series III: Graphic Images
  - Prints
    - Events (#33), 1994 and undated, 35 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH429 - PH464 (Box-folder 6/86)
    - Events (#35), late 1940s 1979 and undated, 11 color prints and 22 black-and-white prints; AFC 1995/015: PH465 - PH500 (Box-folder 6/87)
    - Events (#36), 1950s 1958 1976 1980-1981 1983 and undated, 25 black-and-white prints and 9 color; AFC 1995/015: PH501 - PH534 (Box-folder 7/88)
    - Events (#37-40), 1977 1979, 1980, 1985, 1990s and undated, 20 black-and-white prints and 16 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH535 - PH585 (Box-folder 7/89)
    - Events (#41-47), 1986 1989 and undated, 7 black-and-white and 14 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH586 - PH609 (Box-folder 7/90)
    - Events (#48), 1992 and undated, 20 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH610 - PH629 (Box-folder 7/91)
    - Events (#49 - #50), 1940s, mid 1970s, 1978, 1985, 1988, 1990s and undated, 3 black-and-white and 38 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH630 - PH670 (Box-folder 7/92)
    - Events (#51), 1949, 1952, 1978 and undated, 9 black-and-white and 4 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH671 - PH685 (Box-folder 8/93)
    - Correspondence, 2001 and undated, 34 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH686 – PH721 (Box-folder 8/94)
    - Fun Finders Advertisements and Information, 1977, 1980s, 1990 and undated, 21 black-and-white and 4 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH722 – PH747 (Box-folder 8/95)
    - from Published Materials, undated, 9 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH748 – PH756 (Box-folder 8/96)
    - Early Fun Finders, 1940s and 1950s, 33 black-and-white; AFC 1995/015: PH757 – PH789 (Box-folder 8/97)
    - Indoor Events, undated, 52 black-and-white prints; AFC 1995/015: PH790 – PH842 (Box-folder 8/98)
    - Dance Partners (1 of 5), undated, 24 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH843 – PH887 (Box-folder 8/99)
    - Dance Partners (2 of 5), undated, 16 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH888 – PH912 (Box-folder 8/100)
    - Dance Partners (3 of 5), 1989, 6 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH913 – PH925 (Box-folder 8/101)
    - Dance Partners (4 of 5), undated, 1 color print; AFC 1995/015: PH926 – PH937 (Box-folder 9/102)
    - Dance Partners (5 of 5), 1986, 1989 and undated, 24 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH938 – PH961 (Box-folder 9/103)
    - Indoor Event, undated, 22 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH962 - PH985 (Box-folder 9/104)
    - Indoor Event, undated, 14 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH986 - PH999 (Box-folder 9/105)
    - Indoor Event, undated, 5 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH1000 - PH1004 (Box-folder 9/106)
    - Indoor Event: FBI Special, 1985 and undated, 9 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH1005 - PH1013 (Box-folder 9/107)
    - Indoor Event: Music Maestro, 1984 and undated, 10 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH1014-PH1023 (Box-folder 9/108)
    - Indoor Event, undated, 24 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH1024-PH1047 (Box-folder 9/109)
    - Indoor Event: Sons of Norway, undated, 16 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH1048-PH1063 (Box-folder 9/110)
    - Outdoor Event, undated, 8 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH1064-PH1071 (Box-folder 9/111)
    - Outdoor Event: Bear Creek Park, undated, 12 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH1072-PH1083 (Box-folder 9/112)
    - Outdoor Event, 1984, 8 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH1084-PH1091 (Box-folder 9/113)
    - Outdoor Event: Winslow Court, 1988, 4 color prints; AFC 1995/015: PH1092-PH1123 (Box-folder 9/114)
    - Events undated, 5 color prints; oversize (Box-folder 9/115)
      Black-and-white annotated photocopies of photographs PH1124-PH1128.
    - original video jackets, MV01-MV06 (Box-folder 9/116)
  - Painting (Box 11)
    - The old barn by Hal Hildebrand, 1 14.5 x 17.5 in. painting
      Framed painting of The old barn, built in 1929-30, at Rock Ledge Ranch-Heritage Site Colorado Springs, Colorado.
- Series IV: Moving Images
  - Fun Finders: Traditional Square Dancing, 1 U-Matic; AFC 1995/015: MV12
  - Elementary Fundamentals, 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 100 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV01
  - Fundamentals II, Part 1, 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 116 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV02
  - Fundamentals II, Part 2, 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 60 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV03
  - History in Action, 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 50 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV04
  - Living History, 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 30 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV05
  - Henry Ford Era, 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 98 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV06
  - Western Cowboy and ‘Pappy’ Shaw Era, 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 94 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV07
  - Event #40, Bancroft Park (Aug. 29, 1989), 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 123 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV08
  - Event #41, The “Hoedown-Aires” perform in Acacia Park (Aug. 31, 1989), 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 96 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV09
  - Event #49, Bancroft Territory Days (1987), 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 120 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV10
  - Event #49, Bancroft Territory Days (1989), 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 25 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV11
  - American Folk Dance Heritage (Pioneers’ Museum), 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 7 minutes 33 seconds; AFC 1995/015: MV13
  - Pioneers’ Museum b-roll, interviews, local TV news pieces, 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 7 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV14
  - The [Reminisce] Hitch and Fun Finders (May 14, 1994), 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 120 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV15
  - Copyright statements, [Reminisce] Hitch closing statement, 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 3 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV16
  - Introductory banners/Contra + Square, 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 4 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV17
  - Alexander Film Company (1960s 7-up commercials), 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 6 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV18
  - Alexander Film Company (1960s 7-up commercials), 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 23 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV19
  - Alexander Film Company (1960s car and 7-up commercials), 1 VHS cassette, sound, color; 1/2 in. 57 minutes; AFC 1995/015: MV20
- Oversize Items
  - Events (#1 - #5), oversize (Box-folder 10/117)
  - Events (#6 - #10), oversize (Box-folder 10/118)
  - Events (#11 - #16), oversize (Box-folder 10/119)
  - Events (#17 - #20), oversize (Box-folder 10/120)
  - Events (#21 - #29), oversize (Box-folder 10/121)
  - Events (#30 - #35), oversize (Box-folder 10/122)
  - Events (#36 - #39), oversize (Box-folder 10/123)
  - Events (#40 - #51), oversize (Box-folder 10/124)
  - Events, oversize; AFC 1995/015: PH1124 – PH 1128 (Box-folder 10/125)
Index
Events #1: Recreational, Acacia Park
Events #2: Special Program, Pikes Peak Square Dancers
Events #3: Special Program, Broadmoor Hotel
Events #4: Instructional, First Basic Class
Events #5: Special Program, Fun Finders (KRDO-13 show)
Events #6: Recreational, Circle Y (local YMCA)
Events #7: Group, Fun Finders Exhibition Team
Events #8: Movie, Comes a Horseman
Events #9: Instructional, Circle Y (local YMCA)
Events #10: Recreational, Fun Finders Festival
Events #11: Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders
Events #12: Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders
Events #13: Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders
Events #14: Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders
Events #15: Special Program, Fun Finders Crossroads
Events #16: Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders
Events #17: Instructional, Fun Finders
Events #18: Recreational, Fun Finders
Events #19: Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders
Events #20: Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders
Events #21: Special Program, Fun Finders Colorado Dance Festival
Events #22: News Coverage, Fun Finders
Events #23: News Coverage, Fun Finders
Events #24: Recreation, Fun Finders Contra
Events #25: Reunion, Fun Finders
Events #26: Reunion, Fun Finders
Events #27: Reunion, Fun Finders
Events #28: Reunion, Fun Finders
Events #29: Reunion, Fun Finders
Events #30: Exhibit, Fun Finders Swing Your Partner
Events #31: Special Program, Fun Finders
Events #32: Instructional, Fun Finders
Events #33: Special Program, Country’s Reminisce Hitch
Events #34: (not received)
Events #35: Callers/Instructors, Fun Finders
Events #36: Bands/Groups/Orchestras, Fun Finders
Events #37: Special Program, Mall of the Bluffs Promotion
Events #38: Special Program, Colorado Deaf and Blind School
Events #39: Special Program, East/West Sharing
Events #40: Recreational, Fun Finders
Events #41: Recreational, Fun Finders
Events #42: Informational, Letters
Events #43: Informational, Music Book and Orchestra
Events #44: (not received)
Events #45: Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders
Events #46: Recreational, Fun Finders
Events #47: Recreational, Fun Finders Penrose Hospital
Events #48: Recreational and Instructional, Fun Finders Elderhostel Programs
Events #49: Special Program, Territory Days
Events #50: Special Programs, Fun Finders
Events #51: Callers, Fun Finders